thecelebritycafe.com 2015-12-08

# Privacy Policy | Your entertainment news source since 1995.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers** **UPDATED 6/24/2015**

This policy covers how TheCelebrityCafe.com (“TheCelebrityCafe.com”)  
treats information which personally identifies you (personal  
information) that TheCelebrityCafe.com collects and receives. The  
personal information we collect may include your name, address, phone  
number, or e-mail address. Once you provide TheCelebrityCafe.com with  
personal information, you are not anonymous to us. 

There are several links from the TheCelebrityCafe.com site to third  
party information and service providers who may collect personal  
information from you in order to provide you with information or  
services. TheCelebrityCafe.com has no control over the privacy policy  
of any third party company, so please examine their privacy policy  
prior to submitting any personal information. This privacy policy only  
applies to the TheCelebrityCafe.com web site. 

**Information Collection and Use**

**General:**

When you read stories at TheCelebrityCafe.com, TheCelebrityCafe.com does not collect any personal information from you. 

TheCelebrityCafe.com collects personal information when you submit  
feedback or enter a contest. We may also receive personal information  
from you, for example when you: respond to an email requesting  
feedback.

When you visit TheCelebrityCafe.com pages, we may collect certain  
information about your visit from your browser, including the Internet  
Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet, the date  
and time you access the TheCelebrityCafe.com site, the pages that you  
access while at the TheCelebrityCafe.com site and the Internet address  
of the site from which you linked directly to the TheCelebrityCafe.com  
site. TheCelebrityCafe.com aggregates non-specific visitor information  
for statistical purposes, such as which stories are most popular, and  
which stories are read more frequently. 

This information is used to help improve the TheCelebrityCafe.com site, analyze trends, and administer the site. 

TheCelebrityCafe.com uses your personal information for the following  
general purposes: to determine a winner to contests, to respond to your  
feedback and to alert you of winners to a contest you’ve entered. In  
addition, we use your information to send out our weekly newsletter.

TheCelebrityCafe.com uses aggregate and non-personal information to  
conduct research and to provide reports for TheCelebrityCafe.com  
business partners and customers. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

TheCelebrityCafe.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information  
about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to  
provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your  
permission, or under the following circumstances: 

You elect to receive information from contest sponsors by checking the  
“opt in” box for that contest. TheCelebrityCafe.com will share your  
personal information only as you have elected. 

Advertisements served by third party Internet advertising technology  
companies, appear on pages throughout the TheCelebrityCafe.com site.  
Some advertisements may request personal information directly from you  
or take you to web sites that may request your personal information.  
TheCelebrityCafe.com has no control over its advertisers’ privacy  
policies, so please examine the privacy policy of any company  
advertising on the TheCelebrityCafe.com site prior to submitting any  
personal information. In addition, some ad-serving companies may place  
or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and may use information  
about your visits to the TheCelebrityCafe.com site and other web sites  
in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest  
to you.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Please be aware that when you provide personal information to  
TheCelebrityCafe.com and authorize TheCelebrityCafe.com to share the  
information with a third party, your personal information becomes the  
property of TheCelebrityCafe.com and/or the third party.  
TheCelebrityCafe.com and/or the third party may use your personal  
information to process your request and provide valuable services.  
TheCelebrityCafe.com will only share your personal information with  
third parties under a confidentiality agreement or similar arrangement  
that restricts the third party from sharing your personal information  
with others. 

**If you do not want your information to be used for marketing by or a  
third party, do not “opt in” or agree to such use when you provide your  
personal information through the TheCelebrityCafe.com site. If you do  
not want your non-specific information used for marketing please do not  
submit your information through our contests.**

Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications  
from a third party, your information will be subject to the third  
party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that  
third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third  
party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use  
information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party  
that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle  
your information. 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to  
establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
We may also transfer personal information about you if  
TheCelebrityCafe.com is acquired by or merged with another company. 

Based on client activity or on information that has been provided,  
TheCelebrityCafe.com may display targeted advertisements on the  
TheCelebrityCafe.com site, but TheCelebrityCafe.com does not provide  
your personal information to the advertiser in order to display the  
targeted ads. TheCelebrityCafe.com and third-party advertising  
companies note some of the pages you visit through the use of pixel  
tags. TheCelebrityCafe.com and third-party advertising companies (which  
may include network advertisers) may use information (not including  
your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits  
to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about  
goods and services of apparent interest to you. The information  
collected by third-party advertising companies through the use of these  
pixel tags is not personally identifiable. 

TheCelebrityCafe.com site content is also integrated into other web  
sites. These web sites may collect personal information from their  
visitors that may or may not be used in conjunction with the  
TheCelebrityCafe.com site content. Prior to supplying any personal  
information to any third party company linking to TheCelebrityCafe.com  
site, please read and understand their privacy policy. 

**Cookies**

TheCelebrityCafe.com lets other companies, including business partners  
and companies that show advertisements on some of our pages, set and  
access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their  
cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. 

Advertisers or other companies may have access to  
TheCelebrityCafe.com’s cookies. You have the ability to accept or  
decline these cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies,  
but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if  
you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to  
fully experience the interactive features of this or other web sites  
you visit. 

**Protection of Minor’s Personal Information**

TheCelebrityCafe.com is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from minors. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

TheCelebrityCafe.com may occasionally update this privacy policy. When  
we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the  
privacy policy. If we make such changes to this privacy policy, we will  
place a prominent notice at the top of the privacy policy and you will  
also see the word “Updated” next to the Privacy Policy link on the  
front page of the TheCelebrityCafe.com site. We encourage you to  
periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we  
are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your  
continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy  
policy and any up-dates.

**Social Media Addendum:**

Our Websites contain several links to or integrations with other websites, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Disqus, Tumblr, etc., whose information practices may be different from ours. 

TheCelebrityCafe.com, LLC, its officers, directors, partners, affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, agents, representatives, vendors or suppliers are responsible for the content, privacy policies, products, services, reliability, viewpoint or accuracy of information on any such websites. Third party websites that are accessed through links on our Websites or integrations with other websites have separate privacy policies. 

We have no responsibility or liability for the policies implemented by third parties on their websites. You should contact those third parties directly to ask questions about their privacy policies.

If you enter or choose to leave our sites and go to outside websites, your visits and actions on those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.  
We do not control and are not responsible for the collection of personal information by third party websites, including websites owned or controlled by our preferred financial partners, advertisers, vendors and/or websites not controlled or authorized by TheCelebrityCafe.com. Third party websites that are accessed through links on our Websites or integrations with other websites have separate privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for the policies implemented by third parties on their websites. You should contact those third parties directly to ask questions about their privacy policies.

If you enter or choose to leave our Websites via links to other non-TheCelebrityCafe.com websites, your visits and actions on those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
